var questions = [
    {
        "question" : "Web pages are designed using?",
        "option1"  : "HTML",
        "option2"  : "CSS",
        "option3"  : "JavaScript",
        "option4"  : "jQuery",
        "answer"   : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "___ makes websites dynamic?",
        "option1"  : "CSS",
        "option2"  : "HTML",
        "option3"  : "JavaScript",
        "option4"  : "Bootstrap",
        "answer"   : 3
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is HTML user for?",
        "option1"  : "Skeleton of website.",
        "option2"  : "Design a website.",
        "option3"  : "Make website dynamic.",
        "option4"  : "Database of a website",
        "answer"   : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which CSS property changes background color?",
        "option1"  : "colour",
        "option2"  : "bgcolor",
        "option3"  : "color",
        "option4"  : "background-color",
        "answer"   : 4
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which selector selects all the elements in CSS?",
        "option1"  : "*",
        "option2"  : "+",
        "option3"  : "$",
        "option4"  : "#",
        "answer"   : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is the value of a  in a+=b where a=10 & b=5?",
        "option1"  : "10",
        "option2"  : "5",
        "option3"  : "15",
        "option4"  : "20",
        "answer"   : 3
    },
    {
        "question" : "What does 'document' denote in a JavaScript statement?",
        "option1"  : "JavaScript file",
        "option2"  : "CSS file",
        "option3"  : "HTML page",
        "option4"  : "XML document",
        "answer"   : 3
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which function is used to calculate an expression?",
        "option1"  : "calculate()",
        "option2"  : "calc()",
        "option3"  : "evaluate()",
        "option4"  : "eval()",
        "answer"   : 4
    },
    {
        "question" : "How do you call a function?",
        "option1"  : "call.function_name",
        "option2"  : "function_name.call",
        "option3"  : "call(function_name)",
        "option4"  : "function_name()",
        "answer"   : 4
    },
    {
        "question" : "JavaScript statements should end with a ...?",
        "option1"  : "Comma",
        "option2"  : "Semicolon",
        "option3"  : "Period",
        "option4"  : "Exclamation",
        "answer"   : 2
    }
];
